



Burnaby, BC V5B2W6

d986000777@gmail.com

604 379 6266

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Efficient Junior Python Developer with 2 years of experience in challenging development environments. Excellent communication and organizational abilities with a resourceful approach to solving diverse problems. Deadline-driven and knowledgeable professional with a strong desire to learn and contribute to team success. Successful at improving usability, performance, and functionality by applying skills in HTML and CSS. In-depth understanding of REST APIs, OOP, ORM, MVC architecture, and related best practices. Collaborative and hardworking team player with critical thinking skills and a systematic approach.

SKILLS SUMMARY O

Database

Microsoft SQL Server
PostgreSQL

Visio

Data Modeling

Operating System

Linux Windows macOS

Microsoft Office

Web DevelopmentExcelCSSWordHTMLOutlookJavaScriptPowerPoint

Flask(Python)

Express(Node Js)

Version Control

Git and GitHub

Language

bash **Development method**

Python Agile, Scrum

TDD

CI/CD

CircleCl Virtual Systems

Heroku Virtual box VMware

Cloud

Azure Cloud Services Network

AWS TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP knowledge

Wireshark

Ubuntu Linux Server

EDUCATION

Computer Information Technology Diploma (EXPECTED IN 04/2022)

British Columbia Institute Technology, Burnaby, BC

- Lead a 6 members team to recreate Plants Vs Zombies with Python in one month.
- Designed and developed a Heroku web server to store and sort players' scores with the PostgreSQL database.
- Created multiple game unit models and a game controller.
- Unit test and integration test for the whole project
- Create websites with HTML and JavaScript.

Undergraduate | Computer Science (09/2012 - 04/2015)

Western University, London, ON

- Majored in Computer Science
- Minored in Human Resource Management
- Designed mini car race game with Java

Certificate | Culinary Arts Certificate (09/2015 - 06/2016)

Commonwealth College, Winnipeg, MB

- Learn the art and delivery of an exceptional culinary experience.
- Gain knowledge and skills in classic cooking fundamentals as well as current industry trends, taught by passionate chef-instructors.

WORK HISTORY

SHIFT MANAGER

03/2017 - 01/2020

Za Pizza Bistro | Winnipeg, MB

- Excelled in every store position and regularly backed up front-line staff to keep expertise fresh and relevant.
- Tracked receipts, employee hours, and inventory movements.
- Kept employees operating productively and working on tasks to meet business and customer needs.

SUPERVISOR

07/2016 - 01/2020

Moxie's Grill & Bar | Winnipeg, MB

- Created efficient work schedules for each team member to maintain deadlines and keep shifts properly staffed.
- Applied strong leadership talents and problem-solving skills to maintain team efficiency and organize workflows to meet any daily demand.
- Oversaw and optimized work of 8+ line cooks performing high-quality cooking work.
- Identified individual employee's unique work styles and adapted management methods.